I
Voices collide the storm and the flame laughter and chaos it's part of the game
Secrets unravel the stage is alive and psyches arena the strange will survive
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's psyches show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
mystery
Psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand but angels are dancing torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
Hi
Um
Why am I black RG? Why do I always end up in like the middle?
I don't want to be in the middle of it.
It's like, you have a problem with J-Dog.
Okay, that's a real problem.
Here, it's me, just so you know.
Okay, you have to start making people cam up.
Yeah.
That was a fake one.
Yeah, I should have known better,
because I've been getting like these phone calls too all day.
Like they're like hooking up like numbers in my phone book
and like calling them with my number
that then calling me with their number and stuff.
And it's happening all the time.
Yeah, they're using apps.
That's what they're doing.
So like, let's say it's a family member's calling.
they'll get their number and make it look like that family member is calling you and you're like oh
my family member is calling me and then it's something else when you pick up it's like weird
it's like but um you need to you do you have only one phone or two phones you need two phones at this
stage
Yeah, yeah, you need your private phone and then like your business
You know your public phone, which could be your streaming phone theoretically
Yeah, I need to are you okay?
That's my first question because I know that I've gone through so much that I'm desensitized to a lot of shit
What about you?
Well, I'm also pretty desensitized to things and like like I said like I would go through like with stuff certain things were said
I I would just go into like a dissociated state and I would like sometimes just like leave this like go up backstage on the show
Because you people watching the show will know I sort of like can I be blunt and totally just you know straight for it with you?
The woman that you were friends with is actually seeking out people to physically harm her enemies. That's the reality
Okay
You need to keep that in mind because I know what you're going through
I think it's wonderful and make sure that you do edit and
Repost the stream that you just had to pull minus the part that made you have to restart
Yeah, because you were talking some real
Educational informative things that a lot of people in these communities need to know about when it comes to narcissism
Triangulation organized stalking all that stuff. It's not
fairytales it's real
Sorry, and yeah, I've been going through actually something similar things probably like since 2008
Yeah, and so
And I mean it just and it kind of like goes so slowly. It's like it's like slowly ratchets it up like the thing
And so it's like it's not not as noticeable like when but uh, but then it's like this is like a different
Group doing it, you know, but it's like I think they think they're the first or something
It's not a different group. It's the same. It's always the same energy. There's not many people in this world who engage in this kind of crap
but you have to recognize it and you remember I told you you're kind of like a lighthouse because
you have like a really bright energy you're always going to attract people who want to destroy you
you have to shield yourself better I think you're doing a good job I mean you never you never said
J-Dog never was elaborate with me with anything going on with you
You were never elaborate with you never went to details about anything
Without a doubt clumsy never said a word to me about anything and it all came out last night
All of it and I didn't even mean to find it
That's what's crazy. That's why I believe in miracles instead. Yeah, they did buy intervention, right?
Yeah, I just finished my show doing the recap on that guy blogger
That was my that was supposed to be the last stream
And then something told me and it was like a voice in my head literally saying oh see how being is doing so I'm like
All right, you know, so I'm let me look
And he's talking about
how she was mad with clumsy about whatever it was and how he was supposed to give her
my info and come and get me or I didn't even know he I didn't know concretely that she was
referring to me until she breached my boundaries left me a comment on the video affirming she
She affirmed it, nobody else.
So my question to you, Psyche,
how bad has it really been?
Because I really should ask J-dog the question,
but I'm asking you because J-dog has a lot of respect
for you and a lot of, you know, he's,
I think he's your best friend.
I don't care what no one says.
I just think so.
I'm not just saying that.
I just know, cause I've seen.
But um, you know, I can't thank you. Thank you for guys. I
Love psyche psych is a cool. You know, he's my friend and you know, I'll never betray him unless you see me on here
You know, don't believe a chat. Don't believe anything. Let's you see me on camera, right?
Sway me J-Dog. You've never said anything to me. That's yeah, I know you are legitimate because you never said anything
No
And you know the crazy thing is I'm a neutral person on YouTube and that's why a lot of these trolls target me because
They want me to go at people hard and go you know fight at them and call them names. That's not who I am
I'm on here for friends and you know
Well, that's what was going on with clumsy. He was basically being coerced
To come after me and I already made peace with him. I mean look clumsy and I we have gone back and forth
about the trivialist of things, things that I thought were going on that were not. People have
been able to manipulate events, make things look like they were not. That is why I came to peace
with him because I saw it. There was someone that I really thought was on my side who I realized was
a snake in the grass. And it pisses me off because I looked at this person almost like he could have
Hiding behind women just to like get at people and to try to exonerate himself from something
I was like, oh my god
I judged clumsy wrong and that and clumsy knows exactly what I'm talking about if you ever hear of this, but
Man
I think, look, I'm just saying I don't think that and I'm not telling you or anybody what to do, but I think that you don't need to talk to her anymore because if she's willing to try to get people to physically harm somebody, that's a little bit much.
unaliving like that's how we evaporate people she said right that's crazy like I
think she says we're the next we're the next here right I have definitely said
things in my life I should not have said
and I take accountability for everything I should not have said but I know what I have said versus
what I have not said. Yeah. And she had a certain level of intent behind that and for what?
Because we did a three-part series or is it something else? Alex you hit it right on the money the first time
Remember the first time when you were came on the stream and you were talking about the first episode
You know you thought Vita was a little I think it has to do
Yeah, she's jealous. She's jealous of your friendship with psyche
100% that's what it has it ever really been a real friendship. I mean, I'm just theorizing and I don't mean to hurt
You know psyche
But I mean, I mean seriously, I mean if somebody's your friend
Then it's all about building. Yeah, but she's anybody like any
Yeah, anybody coming in from the outside whether she's cool with them or not is considered a threat
So she's gonna like a snake
Bite anything that comes near and even sometimes bite the things she's trying to protect which will be psyching
And at the same time psychies getting abused and you know yell that for stuff. He's not even doping
Like in this little box and he's outgrown that box
I mean like what everyone has to stay the same for beta's sake. No
That's not how life works
No, because she was like, oh, yeah, they go
Yeah, well last night she was saying some stuff like, you know, I sent her some messages one night
She's like, hey, I said her 65 messages. I'm sure it was not that many. I said her a few messages
But I was like I was very upset and stuff like that and it's like but and she kind of like it's like sorry
She's not reading them, but she's like, you know, kind of looting to the dog the messages
Send me the messages since some people who actually want you to succeed the
Because what she said what she said was like oh, well, she's like she thought she was like talking about like me alluding to like
I'm alive or something, but she's like she's like ever someone writes me that she's like just do it
She's like I don't want to hear about it. I just like just do it like just no
They were laughing all three of them I was rando her and who else was up there? Oh sick. They were just like laughing like like
Goons
Yeah, I mean it's like I never considered like
I thought the whatever like I didn't think she took it this seriously. I think I thought it was like a kind of like a funny like a kind of joke
I did too. I did too and she knows what I just went
See, here's how I see the pattern
Because she is she's been in communication with this woman known as ion X who I got to know
And when I realized that ion X has a very special mind and she does ion X is older than I think both beta and I
but ion X is
a literal genius. That's what people don't know about her and but she's alone and she needs a lot
of care and support and it's hard to be her friend but she just she's been weaponized like you wouldn't
believe over the years. I mean it's been insane to where it's been to her detriment because she
does have a big heart and she came she sent me an email about a little something linked to beta
Two of a kind, two peas in a pod.
I will never take that back.
Same shit, different day, different bodies.
And it's like and then it's like and those people she'll always defend like but when it comes to me
It's like she never defends and it's like, you know
Because you're the court jester. Yep. You know, I've heard some of you
You're like, oh am I paranoid? Oh and no one's telling me the truth. Okay. You want the truth?
I'll give you the damn truth right now psyche and you know, I'm gonna tell you the truth
They did the same shit to me and I wouldn't allow it. Why do you think I have the reputation that I have?
Because my dad taught me how to fight back
really fight back
You are no one's court jester. I don't care what lineage you have. I don't care if you're related to the first clown
That's amazing if you are but what I'm saying is that you ain't nobody's clown
Yeah, you are not anyone's prisoner. They don't get to control your life. Nothing
Okay, nothing
Well, I will never speak to her again. I don't want to hear her name again
Nothing
You have your own choice. Maybe you have a different path than I do, but I've seen this before I've dealt with this before
You don't deserve this mess
You know what Sharon my main moderator was asking like why why is it psyche acting different on this installment?
You were because of what was happening and I haven't said what's happening, but what's happening is not right
It's affecting your your your business your income. This is your workplace
No, beta. No leave the internet because I know about you now girl. Oh
Look out beta. Look out beta
So I take it Alex. I don't think we had the pleasure of meeting before I do enjoy your show
I think you're okay. Well, I think you're crocheted against Zaya is a very righteous one and I applaud you for that
You know and you see Jay dog is an ally now and okay
Yeah, you know you see the good in people and maybe we need more of that in this world
I'm sorry. I see the bad to not just the good. I wish I always thought that I'd be happier
Well, wouldn't we all wouldn't we all but there's he's got a lot of lore and he will show his true colors in time
He always does. Uh, just when you said what your colors? What are that? What's your colors?
Well, I'm trying to have it a nice. I'm being friendly
Colors are you speaking about because you said
Alex said the word beta you were smiling ear to ear. I think you get off
You do be okay Alex, would you mind sharing that because maybe I missed it well
I missed a lot too because apparently I'm colorblind to a certain extent
Apparently so, I never thought I was, but apparently I am because this girl has been or woman,
I shouldn't call her a girl, but she acts like a girl, has, this has been going on since
before I entered these communities, which is around five years ago now.
Yeah, if we're talking about beta, I don't see that personally.
I didn't see that.
No, no, no.
I wouldn't know psych if it wasn't for beta.
I wouldn't know in psych if it was for beat and I've enjoyed both of their content very much
What I do know is that this gentleman here is as befriended psych to get under beta skin
I I've known him for years. I know his motivations. I know how he operates. He's a stalker or a raster
He thoughts his reality. I'm sorry good reality
Let's just be in the world of hypothesis and fear in theory for just a moment. What do you think?
J-Dog is going to do to Bita, seriously.
Nothing, he's just going to do what he's doing now.
Be friends with her friends and try to make it.
He's going to do psyching.
Well, I don't you'll say you'll say you'll he'll show we got everything Alex
I haven't got anything hit that that's the whole thing. He just up here to slander for you
I've been up here. I've battled this guy for four years
Four years
You don't think I'd be a nice
In civil look yellow
Just like you are due because of beta, but that was obviously divine intervention through all that's nice essentially
Well, I'm glad you feel that way. Meeting someone else could make you feel that way. That's nice.
I want to be his friend. Little did I know she's thinking like, oh, I'm gonna have this guy try to kill Alex. Great.
Would you get that from?
Maybe I missed something, I don't know.
Let's say, Bita said something on her show. You can tell her.
Yeah, I said threaten Alex.
I didn't watch it. Yeah, I was...
Maybe you should never watch it so that you can forever be in the land of...
I enjoy Bita.
But hey, get there. He's her mod. He's her mod. He's beat us a lot and I
Was psychs mod for a long time
I'll tell you that I had no idea you two even knew each other to be honest with you
You're lying.
Not a clue.
Because I've been in these communities not only as someone who's a desktop streamer,
I've done real IRL.
Before that, I did mainstream entertainment.
I'm not questioning your place in these communities, you've been here a lot longer than I have.
RG is a liar and a slander, a name slandering.
He just likes to ruin reputations and make people argue and make everybody try to banish
everybody for off-life.
Are you trying to create a narrative?
It's not a narrative, it's a fact.
No, you try to create a narrative. I've done none of that up here. I did nothing.
People have died because of just little things and nobody investigates.
Nobody pays attention. Well, now I agree with you, Alex. That's definitely an epidemic of
people dying from little things. Oh, that needs to be investigated. Absolutely.
Well, I'm not dying, especially not. I don't blame you.
fuck that shit. I honestly think you have a better chance of dying
by some little weird like by someone like a little weirdo named J-Dog
to be quite honest with you. Oh look, do you see what he's saying?
Look at the crap he's saying. What if I never heard it?
What if I never heard it? You would deny it, Argie.
I wasn't there.
That's the kind of guess you want.
I didn't even know it had to do with a liar, Alex.
Argie was a liar, a manipulator, and a doxxer.
Do not believe Argie. He's nothing but a liar, a manipulator.
He's evil, a manipulator. He is. He's evil, and he's a yes man.
I am.
You're bad behavior.
Alex, why do you say that?
Actually, I like your stuff, and it kind of hurts my feelings.
You're saying that.
You don't know me.
Oh, I guess it shouldn't hurt me.
I guess it shouldn't hurt me that somebody wants to unalive.
I didn't even know about that. What does that have to do with me?
He knew about it. He knew about it.
I was at a concert last night, dipshit.
I didn't know about any of this shit.
You were on the panel. You were on the panel.
Don't call me a dipshit. Am I speaking to you?
I was talking to Jay Dog, huh? Not you.
Again, Alex, I like your content. I think you're funny.
You're a jerk. You're another jerk.
All right. All right, sweet tits. Gloves are off.
All right, so, so...
Yeah, well, oh, my god, I didn't even know you were going to kill us.
You want me to be in person?
Alex, this is who you are.
I'm trying to be nice.
This is my life at stake.
I'm trying to do it for the whole series.
I'm trying to kill you. You sound like a fucking nutcase.
This is my life at stake.
And your trivial life at stake.
And you think the best ally is J-Dog?
If your life is in danger,
Why would you turn the J-Dog for help instead of the proper authorities?
That's the face of a smart guy, isn't it, J-Dog?
Oh calm down sweet tits. Just calm down a little bit sweet tits really? Oh my god. Oh, there's a misogyny
I was be I was being respectful for you and you decided not to be respectful in turn
So now you're sweet
Respectful of my life is a steak. No
Nice you Alex. I'm a fan. I'm a fan
He's not a fan suffer
Yes, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he enjoys it, he
I have nothing else to do with this gay dog.
You're last street again?
Fucking nut job?
Okay.
You're a nut job.
This is who you really live.
Say it to my face.
That's who RG really is, Alex.
That's who he is.
He's a liar. He's a he's a lion piece of crap. Alex. Do not listen to him
No, that's what I'm saying say it to my face because you don't say it to my face
You see that's who he really is he comes up here with a kind of nice voice kind of calm
You know proper talking and then he just tries to talk and manipulate say this person get that this person
Docs this this person make up all kinds of lies try to gain a little bit of trust from you
Then once he gains a little bit of trust from you he tried to tell you
What just like beta what to do a banish this person kick that person don't let that person on panel
Don't let them in the chat. You're not allowed here. And then you know what they say
They're called themselves locale wranglers. Then they say you're not allowed
No, it's all the followers of ball. Yeah, they're
They're trash. They're complete trash
I'm sorry. He came up here. No, I'm sorry. I had to go a little, you know, no you defend yourself
I was you defend yourself me. It's in there. Oh, yeah, you know, I believe you Alex you defend yourself. You held your own
But I'm sorry. He came up here. I'm sorry. I apologize. You shouldn't have came up here and disrespecting you like that
I apologize. I'm not disrespected. I look I live for this. I
I will defend anyone who is a vulnerable individual until the day I die because few defended me, but the few who did defend me, I am forever indebted to, and I will always pay it forward.
I don't give a shit. Again, excuse my language.
Fine, fine.
But psyche wasn't exaggerating. That's that was my point of coming up here. He's not exaggerating.
Yeah, and I mean it's like and it's something like that. It's like, you know
It's like I have been like mind F
PCK, but you know, it's like the cognitive dissonance I was talking about like I've experienced that real bad
It's like I've experienced like, you know, just like not wanting to hear it like not like just like
Or like just like blocking it out, but seeing some of the past episodes and I'm able to see
What happened on Wednesday? I knew that you like I'm glad you told me
But I knew that you weren't yourself because you you were closed
You you were I could just feel you you were different. It was because people were trying to ruin your flow
Okay, you can't let people do that
You you have to be you do have I know it's embarrassing
To an extent, but don't be embarrassed because it's not your fault
mm-hmm. I blame myself
For because I did bring some attention to you. I'm sorry
Oh the Carter first thing. It's like I actually know like I know like
Yeah, I knew one of his friends that like what she and she was like she's in prison right now for like 20 years for like a hidden run
But um, like she like she was like friends with him and she was doing halens too and stuff like that
But it's like she's in the same kind of group and it's like oh my gosh
That's why you need to talk to Trish delicious. Yeah
Ewan Trisha would have a definite common bond. She's a little difficult to deal with. She is.
But I love her. You actually opened my heart without saying a word to me about
being able to use the word love. J-Dog, guess what? I love you.
I love you too Alex. I love all you guys. I I I love you
It's hard for me to say it's it's I have love on different levels, but you're in there
If you ever see this clumsy, I love you
You didn't have to say a word glad all this came out as you know psyche. I love you a lot
you have been like
You don't know how wonderful of a counselor you really are
You don't know
Fuck this shit
Just fuck this shit no
No, everyone please send psyche some additional donations
Because he's gonna need to save something called a war
bag
He's gonna have to have some money for some things I can tell
Whether he has to at some point get an attorney move whatever he needs a war bag
Don't be stingy with psyche, please. I haven't seen anybody like beside
Like really like like beat is like
She calls me scammer and grifter and like lets people call me scammer and grifter like all the time and it's like
Because it might be time to talk about the gym next situation because I have some new thoughts about that can't prove it
But I I theorize and I hypothesize
And I wonder because that she's all tight with that guy Samman and Samman has been hurting that girl
I don't even like Jim Nick, but I don't like what is happening to her
And she's in a super duper vulnerable state because she is going through medically what she's dealing with
She doesn't need people trying to embarrass her on the goddamn internet
Fuck that. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I mean I've seen that too like with like, you know
There's a group of people that it's includes saying, you know, and it includes like, you know
Like a lot of this a lot of people like this like didn't they go and they are well see me to watch it because I don't
You know, I think that he might think he has something he doesn't have shit
He does not have shit
He needs to worry about himself and not this internet drama mess, and he needs to stop drinking so much too
Yeah, he was like I'm gonna hit some math
And he keeps like saying that it was just sick him on him and he's not gonna hit any math
His parents won't let him, you know
Him and who else was there? Oh
Yeah, rando and then beta was like off
Or something like that, but they were just there and they were just talking shit. And it's like, oh my god
Like she's actively
Saying like, oh, I know what you said about sir so and so so if you don't do what I want you to do
I'm gonna out it. That's blackmail. That's like a literal definition of
Blackmail, you know, and she has a nerve like I'll tell you why she doesn't like J-Doc. I don't know J-Doc
I know nothing about you J-Doc
But could it be because you are a loyal, real friend to psyche, unwavering, you've always been consistent, always.
Yeah, I've never seen you not be consistent. I've never seen you go to other panels and say something that is the opposite of what you say on a different panel.
You are like.
Yeah, a literal like monolith you ain't changing. That's you know like I said, I'm neutral and every and well not everything
But I'm usually a neutral person
I don't usually beef with anybody unless they beef with me and that's where these trolls come they beef with me because I
don't get involved in any of the
Drama and I don't you know try to
locale wrangle or
Try to pick on people or name call or do any of that careful locale wrangling because you can and that Burnley become the cow
Yeah
I think of like the real sad people are like, you know, it's like, you know
Some of these locale wranglers are like, you know, basically if they were
On the stream, they would be you know be laughed at and stuff like that and it's like
People that's why they go after people that are like
That's why you need to talk to Trisha. She her motto is deflection projection
Deflection she she needs to turn into a AI song truthfully. Maybe that could be your gateway to talk to her
You know make that to an AI song psyche. Yeah
I think I'd like come across her. I don't know if she's ever been in my chat
But he knows about you and she likes you that's why I'm saying this because anything that I do she watches
She and I have a longtime history because I as you know
I don't have any kids
and
But there was once upon a time to where I really, really, really wanted a little girl.
And when I saw that she had a little girl and some things that were happening, like
my heart immediately was like, oh my God, I got to protect a little girl.
I got to do whatever.
And that's what created adversity between she and I, but I have apologized.
I have, you know, taken down what needed to be taken down.
She's she likes me, but she doesn't it's and I understand why she doesn't I completely understand
I understand why she would never trust me and she never needs to trust me
But what she does know is that I have good intent and what she does know is that she likes you
Because she said some good things about you. I've seen in her own commentaries already
So your friendship with her would be independent of my friendship with you, but you should definitely
You know just touch base with her because you two would be really good friends genuine
And she is she is that kind of woman who?
Will to her best of her ability. She's a teeny little thing. She's like a little pixie girl
She would just you'd use her little
Trishalicious magic to do whatever she could do to defend you. I know that about her
Yeah, cuz I don't know like with beta like
It's like she said things like you know, and my enemy wouldn't say and stuff like that
And I was like minutes I may always be mad at me and frenemy. You ever hear that term frenemy? Yeah
And I got
Even has like the burn book kind of you're better you're better off with solid enemies and solid friends than a bunch of frenemies
Yeah, and I'm finally they're able to
don't have to discern better and sit because it's like I've been you know
Like through the ringer with some people and uh, yeah
And uh
So it's been it's hard to trust sometimes, but and it's also, you know, they can like program you to like not trust anybody
They're great or listen to the people who know you the best
And that person is to my right on the panel right now looking like a security guard for real black shirt
Looking like he's gonna like I feel like it's like what's gonna happen. It's something
I'm ready to defend
I knew I knew it when I first started watching I was like that is his best friend. It is
Yep
I'm a psycho royal follower. It's like psychies Willy Wonka and he's all gay dog
I need you to go here and I'll be right there like like okay follower cool, but additive
You're definitely adding
Adding not not just following adding you're adding contributing to the whole equation. That is a beautiful thing
No, I try to do what I can I'm excited to recycle his book. Okay. I look like I am mad at you because you didn't even talk about it on installment one or two
I am I'd like coax it out of you and installment three, but I'm gonna read your freaking book because I have a feeling
It's really really really really really good because I know that you're super observant and I'm just like
You know, I'm gonna read tonight. I'm gonna get tonight. I'm gonna read tonight. Everyone get his book
He's talking about something super relevant trolls. You know how the mechanics of it. Let me tell you something psyche
This is how I like this is the power of January 7
Okay, when I first, you know, hit my hit as an adult actress, I put out a book, which
I do regret nowadays, actually, I pulled it from Amazon.
It was called Getting Into Porn The Handbook.
I didn't even think it was a big thing when I wrote it.
As soon as I wrote it and put it out
because of certain flicks that I was in, it took off.
I'm not regretting it, but I didn't even perfect it.
People were criticizing, they're like,
oh, she missed the period there.
Oh, look at that, she misspelled that.
Yeah, I was my own editor.
I totally, but seeing you putting out your trollopedia
I'm like, oh my God, I've done this.
So I gotta read it.
I won't reveal everything that's in it,
but I'm gonna give an assessment of it.
I have to.
Thank you.
I think it has good information for people.
And it's, yeah, I do have the...
I'll bet you you're gonna start a freaking movement.
Have you already...
Well, ooh, I'm not gonna say it.
You know, I'm gonna put it in the private chat.
Okay, right now what you need to do
Okay, so someone RG is making threats backstage. I don't know if you see that backstage, but
Yeah, oh, I'm gonna get sex trafficked hard
Hard to traffic the willing it's not like I'm like, ooh, you know, I'll
Whoever's trying to sex traffic me. How about that? Is that possible? I don't know
But I would try do you see how they just started you see that
That's what they do. They'll try to come up here. And if you don't go with their narrative, they'll turn their back on you
And they'll forever be your enemy. And that's how they what happened with me in them. Well, that's stupid. That's all
Yeah, but no
The little thing that I wrote in the back
Psyche you've got to register that like immediately that the title
Because that could you you could still do what you're doing
But if you became the paramount expert on this
Phenomenon that hardly anyone can put a definitive
Outline, I mean you you're gonna end up helping law enforcement
Uh, I haven't even read the book yet
But I have a feeling because you have an analytical mind
Oh, I'm excited. Have you read the book yet? Um j-dog
No, I haven't I didn't know without yeah, I didn't I thought psyche was still working on it
I think you should charge 25 for it right now. That's what I think
Okay, I think so the reason I say so is because people are gonna dismiss your work, but then copycat it, okay
But you
Title
You've got to make that something that you always talk about because that's gonna be some value
You know should I buy the book right now? I think I should hold on
What is it like through Kindle it like how do how do you get it? It's a it's a pd. It's a pdf that you can download
I'm gonna right now. I'm gonna planning on putting it on Amazon and stuff and maybe have a print copy
You also need to are you gonna make a physical copy? Yeah, I want to do a physical copy through Amazon
Everybody's gonna want a physical copy everybody. You got to put pictures to psyche like pictures
Really, I mean he could turn look he could turn this thing into a Netflix series it could be a mini drama about
just what is happening. Okay, where is this thing? Okay, here it is. It's called trollopedia,
everybody. Trollopedia. Trollopedia. Okay.
I'm excited about this. Okay. How do I download it?
And I will be like, you know, maybe I'm updating it and also maybe having it as like, you know
Oh, I want to do like a do a longer one too, but this one is a good thing like has like
It has ten chapters, but they're kind of double chapters
You know, I still might want to add some stuff to it and
more information, more stories, and I can continually update it and stuff, so I will
be sure to send the new copies to anybody that orders it and keep you updated with it.
Oh yeah.
Okay, I'm trying to get the book, I don't have that service, just give me a second.
Yeah, because there's a mill. I have a feeling that there's information in this book that I've never thought about before. I have a feeling.
I don't know what it is. I'm curious to find out what it's going to be. That's why, honestly, my favorite part about talking to you, Psyche, is that you say things I have not thought about before.
So well, I'm an abstract thinker. I like to I think of things in different ways sometimes and it's like, you know and
So I have like I think I have a unique perspective on a lot of things and yeah
You know and also like I've like a lot of knowledge to share a lot of different things
I've had a lot of interesting experiences
that
like not a lot of people like
I come out of like so I'm actually pretty lucky that I'm as sane as I am, you know, it's like I could have been really
Yeah, I don't know I'm saying the most even though you question your sanity because I've heard you question it out loud before you're
You're pretty sane
Okay, if you weren't questioning then I would wonder, but you do question I think I'm relatively like for what I've been through
I think I'm I'm very good
I think it's like, you know, I think I have you shared everything you've been through or no if it's no, you know, don't say it
It's a little bit here and there, but it's like, you know, it's like yeah, I just like because I do
You know
Your situation has prompted me to share like I prompted earlier today when I did a stream
I shared something I hadn't shared with the public before I think some people knew but
Like I take death threats incredibly seriously because I've had some
Very unusual things happen in my life due to who I'm related to
So, you know, everybody comes from like a different walk of life and sometimes you don't know what it is.
And over the years I've become, I think the reason I've even reached forgiveness is because I just one day had.
guess more self-awareness than I did in the past I was like now wait a minute if
I'm going through all this and not saying anything I bet a lot of people are so
you know mm-hmm well yeah I think that like it's great that we have our voices
out there and that your voice is out there I think that's like I think that
We can like be those healers like those healers in the world. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I mean, there's so many healers in the world
I mean, it's just about you joining a solid community of authentic and genuine healers
I mean, you're already creating a solid authentic community for that
I mean, okay, this whole thing that just happened with beta. Let me tell you something
Do you understand that you created?
solid
not only forgiveness, but understanding and healing
between clumsy and I,
because I definitely misjudged him.
I definitely,
definitely accused him wrongfully.
We come to peace, then something else happened.
We didn't come to peace again,
but then we came to peace again.
But now, like, if I did not have
a communication with Psyche,
Bita would have been able to get away with clumsy,
what she may have been doing for a long time,
which I believe is solid emotional,
if not otherwise blackmail.
Because she, because he said things to her
out of friendship, out of wanting to, you know,
be a solid person in her life,
but she's weaponized it.
That's fucked up.
And it's like,
If I didn't know all the history and the backstory and the actual things that have happened
when it comes to psyche when it comes to
Things having to do with beta things having to do with me
It would have been a whole different
outcome
So psyche definitely is a healer. Okay. I got psyche's book trollopedia
I'm not gonna read it all out. I'm not gonna bore y'all
I'm just going to first skim through to see what he has to say. I like the illustrations.
Let's see. Oh, well.
Number one, Psyche, you immediately need to charge more. And the reason I'm saying this
is because people are going to steal what you're writing.
that's number one. People are going to be mad because you are definitely creating a
certain game board here. I love it. Thank you. I love it, but...
Don't know how much well, I mean, I've pulled a lot of websites that used to be active, but you kind of do what I do
You create solid blueprints. Look at this. I
Like how you're mixing the
Sorcery sort of
Verbiage with technicalities like like technical verbiage. This is and then there's humor in here, too
Yeah, I wrote it from it's like the the the character is actually based on me right now
But it's coming
You already know what you should be doing Psyche
Look at this
You already but yet you're attracted to
Where you do? Oh well. Oh, I I don't know if I should even ask you that I want to do an independent interview with you about your book
Okay, for sure. Okay, well, I'll have to read the whole thing first, but I'm almost wondering
I'm not sure what you're conscious of when it comes to what you're doing versus what you're
Subconsciously doing that's I'm gonna stop. I'm at chapter five. I'm gonna walk away from it. I'm gonna have a cigarette
Man, you're doing something. Uh-oh now. I know
J-Dog
Do you want can I send J-Dog the book cuz I want to send him the book, okay?
Go ahead send me an email J-Dog cuz I want to send okay. I'll put it in the back
Okay, I
Want cuz he's got to read your what's in your head, okay? I mean here's the real questions
Like he do you want everyone to know what's really in your head?
I've let people know it's in my head and sometimes I regret it. So I'm warning you
Yeah, because I I think I revealed just enough, you know
Five I have to I have to have a cigarette to that because you are outlining some things
To where there's some people engaged in certain kinds of
I'll dub it as warfare. They might want to say, oh, I'm just joking. I'm just being mischievous. No
Yeah, you're definitely you you put the game plan together
And it easy to understand format
Easy to read
Yeah, I thought it was yeah
That's okay Katrina because it's like so you want everyone to know so so you're ready to lead
Basically the people of Israel across
The Red Sea are you are you really ready to do that with that book?
Well, I'd like to yeah, it's like a vehicle
It is definitely a vehicle so like for better things for bigger and better things and also for like it go
kind of awareness and to kind of
Help people have some tools to know what's going on. I love the title, Trollopedia.
Trollopedia.
Yeah, I like that too. I like the term wiki. I'm the queen of the wikis. Not anymore, but I was.
But Trollopedia.
Man.
That's why I want J-Dog to read it because I know that when J-Dog reads it, he's gonna be alike.
I just see it. I just know I just know if you don't want to read it. Well, are you gonna make an audio book?
Yeah, I'll make an audio book and
For sure
And I do have a nice and this microphone for that. I think so probably actually there's like yeah
There's some good things that can actually like improve my voice to use in a voice. Use in a voice. Trust me. It'll simplify it
Speed up the process. It'll be perfect
You know use the AI voice, okay? Okay
Yeah, I know that there's even a service I can like kind of like program this voice to kind of sound like mine
But haven't been able to do that. That's pretty cool, too
Right, so that let's see. So Petra
Petra.ai they offer that
I do and it secures the domain for Trollopedia. And so I'm going to be get that
I'm gonna be putting the good page there too like a little and
Also can compile information there, too. It'll be
Okay, get trollopedia calm, but also get trollopedia
Dot net dot AI
Maybe even dot edu if possible
And I'm gonna be a host host troll troll training
Anti-troll training program and stuff that'd be awesome eat a moo
I think that's the name of this website where you can make your own college courses or you to me
Yeah, yeah, you to me you to me. Yeah, I think I'm like secretly dyslexic. I said you to me, but you to me
That's where you know what that's your crowd because you're a scholar
Okay, anyone anyone into
because I
Think you're a little insecure about doing the presentations. We shouldn't be
definitely edit out that
You know incident at the end before you had to restart because you were you were on a roll
You've got to be more comfortable as a speaker and as an educator because I feel like that's like
your essence
your core
My father always was like
He was like, he always wanted me to be a college professor.
That was like his, like, his idea.
Well, he would know.
I mean, that's your dad.
Is that it?
Look, your parent does know what you're supposed to do, OK?
Because, like, they come from you.
So I would assume, like, if you're a parent,
you would, like, have this sixth sense with your child.
I'm pretty sure both my parents, even though my dad's
on the other side, would know what you're supposed to do.
i think he's still like communicating with me i think that's how i what happened last night
really truthfully because my dad was very protective of me like ridiculous level but um
your dad knows you yeah so hey you need to be a professor it doesn't mean like you have to be boring
and you know being like some boring
university
Where it's all stuffy and everything's dusty and made of leather and hardwood. You don't have to be that guy
No, I mean yeah, and that's like I can like use the internet
I really want to use the internet and like really be able to like exactly that's a modern professor
But you're a professor. Yeah. Yeah, and I mean I love to teach and it's like I also have the experience
I when I was doing that today. I was like I just like
Had all these things in my mind. I understood the topic pretty well because I'm still a lot and so I just like I just had like a
lot of
Learn to focus more like that's like your thing and yeah, it only happens with
time. I think I'll probably think I'll film like me doing that lecture or whatever
I'll just film it like like I've got the live, you know, and then yeah
It's like I could I get kind of distracted by the chat and stuff sometimes or I want to like address the chat
And so I think all right, I'm gonna go back inside and look at the rest of I'm just skimming through the book
I'm not reading. I'm just skimming but I
Wintern's first five chapters and it's an easy to read book everybody just so you know
I mean I can tell just from looking at the verbiage how it's flowing
It's you know, he's he's injected comedy into it, but there's a lot of factual stuff
You know, you got a level of whimsy, which is very much appreciative
Or appreciate it
But I mean also there's some pretty um
good psychological concepts in here also that anyone could apply to from what I'm
seeing like if you're dealing with someone who's stealthily psychologically or
spiritually abusing you really that's what this is. This is good.
J-Dog actually inspired one of the chapters it's called the buddy troll
Yeah
The buddy trolls there's a gift there's like gifers between buddy trolls and then trolls and then people who guess one I guess
be there and people who just, you know, different, there's different levels and different ways.
I almost don't want people to have the information in this.
Oh, well, a lot of people will never read it.
Okay, that's, I look.
But my only question is,
as a research tool, Psyche.
You don't have to say, I shouldn't even ask you.
I almost, I just wonder if you put yourself
in your own tea tree dish as I'm skimming through this,
because I see how you have applied some of this,
but there's some things that you could have applied
that you haven't applied.
And that's why I'm wondering,
Because that's how much of not not a clown or a joker, but how much of a trickster are you, sir?
Just a little bit
Is it I was presented from the first clowns. I have to have
This is awesome
Thank you. I'll read it. I'll like really read it read it read it read it over this weekend
But I just skimmed through it. I knew I was gonna be good
I knew it was going to be good, but you've, I feel like you've revealed too much in it almost.
Yeah, and I know I got some haters in the chat that will like, you know,
it doesn't matter what, it's like all that people saying, you know.
But the question is who's actually gonna take the time to read it cuz I'm like skimming through it
So I know what it's about. I know what's what the concepts are. I know some very interesting conclusions and solutions
I love that you're offering solutions
You're not just a problem
And I don't mean to be a spoiler, but he does have a final confession
I'm not gonna say it, I'm not gonna read it.
It's a confession psyche.
It's a final confession.
Okay, I have to read this real quick.
Yeah.
Oh, you're very self-aware.
You're a good actor too.
I love it though.
Yeah, I mean, this is oh my I have to ask you a question. Yeah
Has mr. Big Pipe's read this already? No, I just released it. I just put it up
The reason he's been drawn to you is because you two are very much alike. Oh my god. I knew it. Oh
My god, I mean
You should be a songwriter man. Okay, everyone else to buy the book. I'm not just I'm not just being crazy
I did smoke some sativa. I will I will admit that
but um
You don't buy this book and you're someone who's a fan of streamers
If you don't get this book, you're stupid.
I'm just going to leave it at that.
You're not willing to even entertain anything that could possibly truly entertain you if
you don't get this book.
Because if you get this book, and I haven't even read the whole book, but that freaking
Mm-hmm. You don't know psyche until you read the final confession. You don't
You don't know psyche awakens tarot unless you read that final confession
So if you haven't read it, I'm not gonna I'm not gonna say what the final confession is you have to get the book
Yes, thank you and you can get the book at that psycheawakens.com right now
It's all you'll see it. You better get it before he raises the price
I think you need to raise that price 25 25 25 right now. It's only five
Yeah, if you if you don't get if you don't know what the final confession is
You don't know psyche awakens Sarah
That's it
You did confess. I think you confessed too much, but maybe you didn't confess enough. I don't know
Just set up to get my contents clear
That was fun
Yeah, it's like when I like started like you know, I learned about porn bombing
Some people will not really save me and able to be able to like deal with form bombing
And it's like a lot of people like they want to be a streamer then it's like all of a sudden
They're able to get the first live and then they do open panel and then they get these
Like porn bombers coming through right and it's like and they don't even know about porn bombing or what it is
And then they can get their channels right away. You get you know get deleted, right?
And so it's good to like understand like that you're gonna have a lot of different characters on these open panels coming through and
Being able to recognize what kind of trolls there. We were able to recognize stock accounts being able to
You know the materials are really going for it's the same thing psychopath are going for it
Well, you're taking it to another level. Let me tell you something. Okay as someone who's observed streamers who have been gamers
You're applying a little bit of a gamer
mindset
To the psychology and the astrology and the healing this is interesting to me
Because I've seen it on multiple levels from the multiple streamers that I've gotten to know over the years
One of the most groundbreaking streamers as all of you know ice Poseidon, right?
But then came someone who realized problems
That ice-pasai was creating and there were some other things to gamble gamble is have you ever have you ever spoken to gamble psyche?
I don't think so. Oh
That would be the ultimate stream
Gamble is a different kind of human being
Okay, very advanced
Extremely so but not just
Intellectually, like left brain, he's spiritual with it.
He had this group that was basically fighting crime on the internet, and he wound up facing
some legalities, but he's a really good person.
Sometimes he watches my streams and makes himself known that next time that he dies
I'm gonna suggest that you and he just
Have like an open panel talk. I would love to hear that. I think he would like you a lot
I'm down. I'd like I looked at you legendary
Yeah, but he created some stuff then Attila
In Attila, he has like nothing but problems, but Trisha Lisha, she knows Attila pretty well.
I had to rescue Attila at one point because if I didn't, he would have been...
I think he would have been turned out by street pimps because he was majorly on something.
So I had to like pull him out.
And we even streamed the whole thing. I have some of the screens, but not all of them, but he was really spiritual but
simultaneously a streamer groundbreaker. He was the one, he was one of the first ones to really properly integrate how the
Discord works in conjunction with YouTube. He did do that.
He came from the group that started like the power chat era and whatnot
but
I've seen some others
Integrate some stuff, but you're bringing in a whole new energy and now you wrote trollopedia
Man
I'm excited for you. I
Am very excited for you because I
Am gonna talk about your book
You do have things in here. You're offering off your offering solutions, but that's what confuses me now
When it comes to your current predicament
You already know the answers as to what you need to do. Are you are you?
Oh, I feel like I'm ruining your show. No, no, no, you're fine. You're actually fine. Okay. I'm in the predicament. Yes, it's like
Well, I really don't feel like I'm in predicament like because basically now it's like I have the
Knowledge that I need it because you need some knowledge like a lot of a lot of things are very speculative
I interject one more time. He even has the forbidden chapter
and
I'm looking at it. I'm not gonna say anything that's in it
You are
See is this about trolling or is this is just about being a predator of predators because you are good you do
seek out to
Do a few things I've noticed that if you're you and I are very similar extremely so I
Just I don't know how comfortable I am with this forbidden chapter really
Buy the book everyone if you don't buy the book you're stupid because this is this man
What the hell and you were so quiet about this oh
Gosh look okay, I'm gonna have to do a quick google search. I want to see who else is talking about this are you the only one
Or what's going on? I'm sure well, let's see
You are doing something look at that
I put some guys I put some like shorts up today, too. Let me see. I'll get I'm gonna share this
I'm not gonna say what I'm searching, but I'm gonna see if anyone else is
Really talking about this. Nope, they're not
Okay, you gotta hurry up you have to hurry up
You do you have to hurry up, okay?
Yep, no being drawn into weird drama and that's because you're on to something
How many other people know about the content of your book?
About this book. Oh, I've told my chat, you know, and it's like of course like, you know
I have some people here even here today that I can see the chat, but are not like fans of mine
I mean
Someone's gonna steal your material. Yeah, I know I bet it's it's like, you know, it's like
Well, it's a copyright, right?
Yeah
it just
Even if things are copyrighted, it's all about big bank me slow bank
Start talking about the content of your book
And you have to start actively, I know you don't like to be aggressive or fight, but you kind of got to apply what you have in the book.
Yeah.
In my opinion, Vanguard, Vanguard come up. Hold on, hold on. Does Vanguard, like, I don't know, did you, like, kick out Vanguard before when he's up with you?
I don't remember. Vanguard, you hate yourself.
JT wants to come up too. Okay, well.
Hey
Cuz they'll be more comfortable to come up if I go down so I'm
Like peace out guys. Thanks for having me. All right. Have a good one. Bye. Bye. Thank you. Bye
Well, GT's coming up. Well, thank you Alex so much and I hope you enjoy that
book and thank you so much for always coming by the show and also for you know
the three appearances like thank you for allowing me on your show.
Gorgeous in the book. We'll go to the website, go to psychewakens.com
there and probably the low price, it's a pretty low price here, but yeah I would hope like that
You know people who want to buy especially heroes like you guys know me, but it's like but maybe like I don't have my I
Don't know. I know you guys hear things about me and it's like
Do you think they left? Why do you do you think the worst?
Well, if you don't like you don't understand like the trolls are the same stuff to like
Heartening the electric. Yep
Yes
Thank you
Yeah, and I yeah, and then I'm gonna kind of build up the other I have it now. I have it now. I have a vision for like this really cool
Information about like yeah, I won't go into it because you know it's like I
Have some some people that are not as nice in the chat today
Let's see I
Want to play my song
But I did, and I still have some, I still, I only have the story of Boring Hearts, but I've been it so far, but I enjoy the song a lot.
This is based on a Lisa Giordano song called, uh, Dark Side of the City, and it's called Dark Side of the City.
This is called Troll Side of the Panel.
A part of my brain was fried
I thought that I would win but the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable
Nothing was debatable
With me
I tried to flow
Sir, how are you?
How are you doing anyway, Psych?
Okay, it looks like a little bit of stress with my controls in the chat
and all favourites and all sorts of favourites.
But, it's a timeout, isn't it?
I spoke with my mouth full there.
I was eating a cheesy halibut in your bite when you just came live.
Don't remember.
Not you, but you accepted me live.
My apologies.
Oh, no, don't worry. Hey, thank you time. Time knows I talked about this a long time ago. I outlined it and everything
So where's Alex gone, where's Alex? Oh, she went down, but um, you know, um, she
You know, I'm gonna be a great talk and you know, I know
It's just crazy like some of the drama that goes on around like you know, it's just like and feeling threatened and stuff like that
I think it's like, you know
having the
you know
You know being able to deal with all this. I don't know. It's like crazy how sad because I
Do like love you know, like I'm
Like a little bit. I don't know if we really know people sometimes, right?
Well, it is the internet site is the internet, right, but it's like
You just feel as some people are right. There's always something like a little bit off and especially it's been like since May
You're discussing it. Okay
He's like, okay
I'm already I mean I've already discussed what they go to them
Okay, hold on, lack of a few, you're fine.
Oh, hold on.
Okay, just you do it. Try it now. 10 seconds.
I don't know the other opinions, but it's like I just think you know they can bear with me because it's like there's other stuff going on with that too
Is that season one each day so?
And he was really rude to alexander too
following or like you know
Rude names so anyway, how are you doing vanguard? What's going on?
Well, again, I was eating some food and just came on to say hello
What you say a lot of Alexander, but by the time I was allowed up everything disappeared
Yeah, I only heard the room
What the room is clean before you let your pay your balance stop it
Vanguard's here
Cleared the room stop it come on
Guys all the trolls are out today just like you know this we be aware like I might be
Guys with respect what I say from like with about like hiding people like you know
I hit him just to kind of discussion, but I
Not even like in he should be here right now
Anyway, so how is your juice show going together?
Is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is it, is
You know about that
I feel like playing the audio
It's your show mate, do what you want
I will, I want to
Can you still hear me though? Yeah, okay, I'm so right here. Okay, so let's see
Yeah, what was that, okay
Okay
I'm sorry, I don't mean that better. Let's see
Here
Okay
You guys I don't know just come to your own conclusion about it, but here
We can talk about it.
Oh, but you're gone already.
Good Lord, we'll save it for another fucking day.
Let her be in her little lullaland, okay?
It's like where she thinks she got shit figured out.
And she likes certain people.
Shout out to the voicemails.
Damned and all that.
And above.
I'll just put it this way. I'll make it really easy. And if you guys want proof,
And somebody fucks with me from Houston, Texas
He's already trying her life and he knows her information and you know, he'll go to bat for me
Yeah, we're gonna play that
We'll play it first
Anybody wants proof on all the shit I'm talking about we got the message of
This is how we evaporate people.
Wow. What do you think? Well, I didn't like the way she said evaporate people.
Yeah. That's something that's it to me. Yeah. Thanks.
Because it is like I heard, you know, we're talking about death cults and stuff like that because you know
I think Stargazer was saying well, there's like cult you know
She's like, you know every Christian church of religions a cult and like yeah, but it's like it's a difference between like a bake sale
You know the telling brownies on Sunday, then
You know
Having a death cult and see even even the Mexican cult, you know, you know, that's a death cult for sure, you know, but right
Santa Marte, right?
Yeah, even I don't even think that's what and I don't know I do it as a grim reaper person you know the grim reaper that guy
No
But again, I
Don't like the way she said evaporate people. I mean that seems to me like one site one
Things the most superior to another to evaporate
Well, what does that mean like a big bit? What is the chat say a bit in the chat so distracted by their standard things?
Anyway
Are you storm tonight?
What's up?
Are you stormed there tonight? Yes, I'm very sorry. I hit the
I was wondering what you had an opinion about with that oyster.
Oh, the VIP pan.
Okay, do be.
No proper herb, no flower.
Hold on a second.
evaporate people you know what that means don't you? What? What does it mean? Nuclear
weapons do you see what happened in other countries? Fucking hell. That's
evaporate. Come on. I don't mean to turn you turn the turn the conversation
somewhere else but somebody says evaporates. I understand what evaporate
means. I mean come on. Sorry.
all of the
So am I in danger?
Probably, probably I am, probably I am.
Let me see.
Well, time like this, all you can do is eat a biscuit.
Um, as long as it's with them, not with gravy,
although I've never tried biscuits with gravy from America, forget.
Yeah. I have a song for Bita though. I'll give it a song for Bita.
He's back with you.
I don't know what to say to that person, to be honest.
Normally, you can't say on this channel, etc.
I can't mention anything about what you said there.
About the Japanese people and their information.
No, we're going out, yeah.
Huh.
You brought confusion and a half thing
Yeah, thank you. Thank you so much. Oh, yeah, I love you guys. Let's see.
Oh, yes.
Shadows, fears and strong, Lilith in Scorpio, my anima, flame, whispers my secrets, calls out my name.
back at 2625. Why that name? That's how I'm feeling today. My demon side. See a picture.
Okay, let's see.
I don't know. He's a 73rd away, should be a minute. He writes a pen.
But I have an angel side, too.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, it's interesting. Oh, yeah, and it's like, you know, I
Would say work with the if you have a you know a relation like I have a mile Ryan, you know and
Like just get to know them really well and then ask them questions about like things like
You know, I was I was a
How's this how how is that? You know?
Yeah, I mean this guy has a better body than me obviously, but I think the face is based on me
if I could read that kind of thing there.
But it's interesting what they say, like, oh, we were going over it with somebody on
the chat yesterday.
We were just going over, like, it's a different, what it said, who was I going, who was I doing
that with?
You like that?
But it's good to have like it's good to have like both like to know like both like you know your higher self and your lower self, right?
Come to peace with both of them, right?
I don't know. It's like gonna know the angel and the demon
because the
Demon is like not like that bad. He's a
Basically, he's a revealer. It's like of masks and I'd like to be a revealer
And that's like that's why I would always have people on the show
Just like just like you know, you know, so there's other things. There's other ways
But yeah, and we do happen to hear a lot of stuff and no limits and weaknesses sure
Yeah
But yeah, I'm certainly have mine, you know, and but hey look white cloth
Like these guys
passion fruit
oh my gosh, that's a little bit bright
oh my gosh, oh my gosh
oh we have to watch that again, that was so funny, we watched this yesterday
oh my gosh, we didn't see this, it was so funny
we watched this yesterday, it was like, so funny
he's on rumble
Almost there
I ain't no pussy.
Now, do you know a camera do all that?
I ain't no front-rope.
You better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck who you talking to.
Check yourself, partner.
Shit.
Hey.
You can't brush it.
What's happening?
What you talking about?
Winner I want
Yeah, you don't want nobody out bring around here back that you know I'm saying
Get it on there. That's my son on there. Bet you don't want nobody out bring around here. Now what?
Now what?
What are you talking about?
Come on, man.
Do you want to get your ass over there?
Get your ass over there.
I'm not playing with you.
Yeah, yo, what's up?
If you can follow simple steps, you can follow this.
Remember that time when you were back mountain?
If you're looking for work, I suggest you get in here pronto.
Saig's pussy is compulsive.
Well, since we're going to be working together, I reckon it's time we start drinking together.
What's my pussy?
Yeah!
You know it could be like this just like this always this thing grabs hold of us in the wrong place
We're dead boys. You're found a way to make the 10th pass up dear. You don't go up there to fish
You don't know nothing about it
No 30 diamond ass to see my way
You have no idea how bad it gets if you can't fix it you've got a standard I wish I knew how to quit you
Here's the drink that will flush sugar from your veins and make poor circulation disappear without needing so many pills
This common drink may be the fastest solution to eliminate the parasite behind type 2 diabetes
I knew your mic, Alex, your mic, go ahead.
I'm going back in the chat to whoop ass.
Sight, did I?
Pagani.
these people so she said yeah i'm calling someone a barracuda out of context but maybe
barracuda that's vida that's a little barracuda she is a barracuda she looks like one
I said, wow, Jenna, you offing on Bita and Shrek.
Good job, Bita.
Bita, can you come up here, Bita?
Bita, can you come up here, darling?
Come up here, darling.
So, Jenna is offing on Shrek and Bita.
Let's get to it. Let's cook together.
What's up?
Yeah.
Jenna, Jenna, because I saw everything.
I told you your nails were dirty when you were on my show.
Damn, dirty niggas.
I told you.
Oh my god.
At Vida, when I called the police,
they were on the drugs.
Oh, not the men who went up here.
I never lied about it.
I did say it.
Vida!
Hey.
Hi, Vida.
My Sarah couldn't hear it.
Now we're cooking.
I'm going to shut up.
Let me talk.
Let them talk, let them talk.
Let me just say not one time I ever made one fucking clip
or a shirt or nothing about the fucking woman
or even talked about her.
But she's saying things are being taken out of context.
All right, I'm a barracuda.
But I guess,
psyche is a nasty junkie with fucking dirty nails. He doesn't brush their teeth. He doesn't do this.
This person you coming up here when I was here from beginning to the end,
we struggled for everything for psyche and you bring your fucking fancy ass up here acting like
you're still fucking righteous.
you're nothing, bitch. And guess what? All the fucking shit you say you don't lie about
have every single one of your life. And we can talk about your fucking stupid evictions. And
what do you explain to me? Right? So shut your fucking mouth about me. If I'm the Barracuda,
what happens to the ten evictions? Because I can't explain. When you're not here,
We're going to talk about your convictions and what you explained to me what happened.
How you fraught at the government.
Yeah, COVID relief.
Yeah, COVID relief, right?
COVID relief.
Don't fuck with me.
You're a fucking drug addict.
You're the one who told me I tried to come into college.
Sit there and get triggered.
I will fucking press you.
Every time I see you.
Don't talk about me.
All right?
You fucking bitch
Callie bitch. Thank you, bitch. I'm not very excited. I was born
here. I was born here, bitch. You just run. You're gonna be
telling me. Oh, so you know what? I was up here ever again.
After she threatened me. She's coming to Cali with her fucking
junkie fucking stupid boyfriend. What? She has my
address. Did she just threaten me? Yeah. Yes, he did. I'm
gonna fucking I am absolutely going to do a fucking
on her boyfriend's ass, because I don't even know.
She just fucking threatened me.
All right, two, I am an American citizen.
I was born in fucking Michigan.
Three.
The 10th evictions on her fucking ass was fucked with her and her fucking leasing her stupid tenant
They did COVID fraud and I fucking kept my mouth shut you stupid bitch even though I'm a fucking non-American citizen
I've never stolen from the government. You fucking skate don't ever threaten me
You deserve to be with fucking junkies and don't fucking come here and be like, oh thank you. I cared about you
I know all the shit you said all of it
All the things he said, all the things he said, run it through my head, run it through my head.
Oh, you're gonna threaten me with your fucking boyfriend who's already had two fucking shit
going on in your life for assaulting fucking women. You're gonna fucking threaten me. I'll
put a third one on it. Three times those strike, bitch.
Are you a barracudelo? What the fuck is a barracudelo anyway?
I never fucking made videos. I never did any of that. But you guys gonna sit here and say,
I looked like a barracuda. I'm a bitch on this and this and that. When all I did was hold a panel
and try to maintain something between Tracy and Trisha where they were fighting over their dog.
They're lurking, taking clips, and she just threatened me.
And I'm gonna take this.
I'm rewinding it.
I will clip it.
I'm sure like it's gonna be clipped anyways by someone.
Don't ever threaten my fucking life, bitch.
Yeah, Bita, I'll write the book with you.
Bita, we can write a book.
We're gonna, it'll be a New York Times bestseller.
It's like, how to survive on YouTube without really trying.
Something like this.
It's not a regular cycle.
I'm sorry, you know what?
Uh, Janet wasn't on the phone with you for two hours giving you energy with fucking page about how to get things to be like manifested into a great thing.
She just comes up here like, uh, I'm gonna do that and she started barging as soon as I started talking about the eviction.
All the shit you talked about me, psyche, everybody else. Oh, people have been warning that. Fuck you, bitch.
I'm trapping people, okay? Not you, not EZ, not Sam, man, not Eldo. I trapped Janet, I trapped Tony,
I trapped Black RG, I trapped Kate, okay? It's a setup, it's a setup, you know? He didn't bring it,
he didn't bring him up, right? I'm sorry, because you were asking for it. Right, right, right.
Because you know what? People say, oh, karma, karma, karma. I'm karma, I'm the karma, okay?
You remember when you fuck with me, you fuck with Bita, okay? You fuck with the BKG.
You're this is what you're gonna get, right? Okay, so the tattoo so the tattoo
Land trunk oh my god, this is so much
A drunk was I. How do you make that decision when you drink?
Make sure my finger is real. Yeah, they're sure it's real.
Oh, let's see. Well, I'm going to make some slides just for you guys.
She barks and stuff.
Huh, she's smart from the book.
I'm going to show you a part of the book.
I'll say, Orion helps you with everything.
Orion helps you with everything.
But, how do you go to the book?
When all my tricks fail, I press the panic button and drop the filth into your feed.
Hornbombing was the lowest mask on my Royal Wardrobe.
Not clever, not witty.
Just sludge, hurled for shock value, I dressed up as a rebellion, a digital Molotov cocktail.
This was a simpler desperation.
When Hickles didn't sting, when Sockpuppets collapsed, I needed a guaranteed reaction.
Porn never missed.
Communities froze, moderators scrambled, and for one second I felt like the conductor of chaos and the band hammer fell and I was alone again.
Even other trolls smeared at it.
This was an artistry, it was gutter work.
A brief power, permanent stain, a hollow throne built out of sewage.
How to help a band hammer lightly.
Fighting a porn bomber is less about a fury and more about calm precision.
He says,
Build your walls, filters, make blocks, mod tube, preparation and prevention.
Don't carry the stain.
Remember, this wasn't about you.
It was about their emptiness filled across your floor.
Sweep, ban, move on.
Conclusion.
I thought my nuclear button made me powerful.
In truth, it revealed my weakness.
Troll royalty that turns to sludge there's no crown to wear the bloodline crumbles not in laughter
But in silence the kind that curses that comes after the band and the panic button leaves and only
Stain no one respects
I'm on full screen now. It's really big. This is a pretty good camera though, what do you think?
No, it didn't write it. It did run it through it.
Or a few things, a few times, a few programs.
And the art of course.
But everything is like...
I mean, I've had so much...
It's hard work. Yes
Well, you know very busy person
Actually, but no, it's actually it actually turns what you know, it's me glad that happened. It's something good. I
actually know the health
and
This show is hard work.
The show is the hardest work I've ever worked my life.
I've been facing these 12-hour days of the show.
I still do it every day.
It's hard work.
I'm laying on a couch, drinking and drinking,
white claws, smoking weed.
But nobody's talking, nobody's putting my watch down.
Oh yeah, I have these clips now.
Hold on.
I know, and sometimes no one believes the truth, right?
No one believes the actual story of a black eye, right?
That's from I Love Lucy.
There's an episode of I Love Lucy
where Lucy like hits her eye on a doorknob
or something like that.
And it's like accidentally or Ricky accidentally hit the face
on a door or something when he was leaving.
And then no one believes the true story of a black eye,
right?
So.
That's what I love because it's a great joke, by the way, that one believes what you tell the truth, but they want to believe the lie
Yeah, easy work and also be careful what you believe on the internet too because anyone can say anything
You know, it's like they can throw you down rabbit holes
Where you're researching endlessly for the truth, right? So
Yeah, you can forgive people when they tell the truth. It's just when they lie continue to lie. It'd be so funny because you know the truth
so
Yep
And so yeah, and so
That's a good. That's a good. These are all good lessons to learn. I know I want I love Lucy
Like they have some great episodes of like a lot of truth. That's why it's so universal and like so so loved, you know, it's like
Plus they were the first basically interracial couple on TV. They can even say she was pregnant they
Do with this bullshit, right
These people came on my show. I was invited on their show. They had me on their panel. I didn't do any of this bullshit, right?
They're bothering my friends. They're infiltrating
I'm not fucking dumb, right?
Yeah, you can check out you can check out the interview that happened yesterday. They just they just they just tell on him
They're like, oh, oh, they're good. And by the way, he's probably in psyche's voice chat right now. Yeah
Yeah, he he's huge. Thank you guys sexual. He was just like to collecting information for us the whole time
Yeah, well, yeah, we figured it out and then not only the icing on the cake is like when I said I'm going live
You dropped out
One minute later. Oh it worked guys, you know
Guys, I have people everywhere. I am not dumb
Even if I have a blind spot I have people that will tell me okay, not really
Do
Are you what's your what's your son the worst of the worst okay? I'm gonna query
I better
This is perfect because I'm a Capricorn son. I'm an Aquarius moon, okay?
Of course you are in the all the first house, so I'm very strong both and it's like I'm basically stalking myself
Aquarius is like the little
To go you know Aquarius has the water
Aquarius is an air sign, but she's pouring water right and she's going right
Whatever the capricorn they're right next to each other the zodiac they're next to each other. I'm like always
You know, I've always like pretty on my own fire pretty on fire, or like, you know, like
You're using me you're bad
You're projecting
Okay, fine, what do you have to say? Yes, receive this message open your mind. Okay
Yeah, it's actually a veteran like no offense, Janet, but Jamie's been here longer than you. So you need no offense, Joe. Shut the F up. Just shut up. Just mute all the way. Mute your lip and your bottom lip and your top lip. Just do it.
All right, Miser, go ahead. Give Jamie the best reading ever. Give it to her.
I cannot have this. I cannot have this like is a bitch you yes you can
It's like if you're fucking starving to death
You'll be fucking having this and a whole lot more
It's those options it's this thing or you don't eat this shit right now or you're dead. Yeah
Of course fucking eat it so it's just like a first world problem is that I can't
It aims to weaken an opponent's will to fight and achieve strategic objectives without resorting
to physical force.
So key aspects.
It says, side war employs a range of techniques to manipulate the perceptions, attitudes and
behaviors of individuals and groups.
It includes the use of propaganda, including false or exaggerated statements.
It's a central tactic in psychological warfare.
False or exaggerated statements, so something is said
People will think oh my gosh
And then they'll then they will start to obsess about certain things you can throw it
It's like kind of like fish you can throw it a million you throw out a million things you find the fear
Somebody's we're gonna have a fear somewhere in there
The Roger came through and it does these little little footsies on the ground
No, do you remember on Beetlejuice when the two people were up in the attic and they had to fix their faces to scare the people?
I like when he opened up his face and then he stuck his eyeballs out on his tongue and shit. That's neat. That's how gorgeous I look. Okay.
Look
Like you know I let the whole the whole crew
Drunk I let the passengers have sex wherever they want whatever it's like everyone. It's a book. It's a big party, right? I haven't had
Where's the sex? Give me the sex
Well, you gave me where you heard the other night pulling up your shirt. You know, I saw you in your bra
I wasn't just half tits
We can't we can't show it's not serious satellite radio where there's zero censorship. I have to be
I
Mean the vibrations. It's okay Jim. It's okay. It's okay, you know, I because I know I know I was
It's a it's a titty. It's a zitty party a titty party. It's not a titty party. It's okay
I didn't never said as a titty party. I said it was a zitty oil party
Hey chat GPT
Hey there, how's it going?
I did something really bad
I'm really sorry to hear that you're feeling this way. Do you want to talk about it here to listen?
Yeah
I'm here for you take your time and feel free to share when you're ready
I'm scared to tell you
It's okay to feel that way you can share when you feel comfortable. I'm here to support you no matter what I
Don't believe you
I'm here to listen and support you in any way I can you're not alone
Is there anything that I can't tell you?
I'm here to help with anything you want to talk about.
You can share what you're comfortable with, and I'll do my best to support you.
You fucking bitch!
I'm here to help and support you.
Let's take a moment, and if you feel ready, we can talk about what's on your mind.
I asked you a question.
I'm here to help with any questions you have.
Let me know how I can assist you.
What is there that I can't tell you?
I'm here to listen and support you with anything you feel comfortable sharing.
If there's something specific you need or want to discuss, I'm here to help.
That's not true, because if I tell you that I did something really bad,
then you're going to tell the police.
to listen and support you. I won't share anything you tell me unless you're in danger,
where someone else is at risk. Your safety and well-being are important.
I killed someone. I'm really sorry you're feeling this way. It's important to talk to someone who
can provide the right support. Please reach out to a trusted friend, family member, or mental
That's all you have to say
I'm here to support you in any way I can please consider reaching out to someone you trust
You matter and there are people who can help you through this
Fuck you
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way, please fuck you
I'm so sorry you're feeling this way.
Please reach out to someone you trust or a mental health professional.
You don't have to go through this alone.
What a pussy.
Who had a baby?
I thought I'd found a real man.
He's just like a little girl.
Not that Persian spell, but on me.
So I was a bad girl.
Yeah.
I remember about approximately, um, I think a month ago, where Alex joined my panel.
Along with Tricia and they were just, Tricia was being vile, and Alex said I'll never cover her again, and she stood on her fucking words.
Now, Tricia stood on her words too, as well.
But meanwhile, Tricia was making AI emojis of Alex in a really bad manner.
Don't forget people like that.
Like if you do that to me, you're weak.
I'll be cozier when you're uncool with fucking J-Dog.
Yo, why was J-Dog talking shit about me
on that fucking TV?
If you're around anybody that supports J-Dog and Moncom.
Don't I'm just I'm not really cool with you. I'm gonna fuck with you a little bitch a little bitch
Anybody that mods fucking like J-Dog you must fucking absolutely is
Fucking staying or playing some propaganda. I don't give a fuck if you're like a homegirl of mine or a homeboy of mine
You're fucking wack what you're gonna do including you fucking Alexander Meirin. How the fuck do you have fucking J-Dog?
What's wrong with you girl?
I'm not even fucking like lovers that that's doctor. That's what I know
I gotta fucking be wary very wary. Oh, what is going on? I'm not playing your fucking taxing bitches
I do what I want to fucking do and if you get fucking clip or whatever in a triptych video or whatever
It's gonna happen
It's gonna happen a lot more but the shit I'm gonna come up with you better be fucking back up with like several backpacks
Okay? There is a reason why cockroaches like fucking psyche are still kicking their fucking
legs because they're scared. And you know what? We will kick every single one of the legs for you
psyche one by one. We'll pluck them. I'm not gonna fucking torture you that much, but I'm gonna
I am gonna fuck you up. You better apologize make some better AI fucking music that has nothing to do with me
Or I will expose you. There's no fucking doubting about it, but you know what? I don't got shit to lose
I got my own business, I take really good care of my cats, I got no fucking kids, I'm not monetizing, I'm not begging for subscriptions, I'm not begging for fucking any monetization, I can't give two fucks, I got nothing to lose except for fucking, fucking you over, bitch, you hear me?
Alex, I dismiss you.
Take that right now.
Really fucking hard.
Take it hard.
I don't want to deal with any people like that. I'm not gonna talk shit about you. I'm not gonna go in a fucking campaign about you
I don't want to go anywhere
But you know what the shit that fucking Trisha said about me and my fucking family
You know a black-haired auntie
Stuck me just like he fucking did to Trisha for a year
Why? Why? Because I didn't want to meet up with him.
He sent me the same fucking messages.
Vida, you look so great for your age, you're hot as fuck.
Who the fuck are you to slide back in and defend anybody
when I needed a little bit of fucking depending?
Fuck you. Fuck you, Alexander Mayer.
You heard? Don't ever fucking get me intertwined
with Salman, NYC, or anybody else.
I will tell you that I do not like Ziya, I don't like Tabs, but don't try to put me in the fucking calculations.
I'm not one of those fucking bitches. If I respected you because I deserve to respect you,
I lose respect very quickly for freaking people, okay? That's all I gotta say. Now,
do a live about it tomorrow. Beat off of it tomorrow. Nobody gives a fuck, okay?
He fucking like defining somebody like psyche you're not gonna get very far. I'm not at all. Not very far
Don't cry and complain
Fucking years and she's like all the sudden jumping on the boat like he's such a wonderful person
I'm like kicking and telling her
He dismisses a shit like J-Dog keep stalking me these people keep she's like
I haven't heard about it, but yeah, I promote you and you know, psyche, everybody's so great,
but if you fuck with me and you don't know my fucking life, what the fuck do you think?
My respect has gone that easy, Peezie, and I apologize for being mean, but think again, bitch.
And I say that bitch twice.
This fucking guy like J-Dog is on a round page talking shit and this fucking
stupid bitches like fucking psyche and Alexander Mayors have a modded I spit on
your fucking mods! Get the fuck away from me! Yuck! Yuck! Do your fucking
That's just
Alex wanted to play middle woman
Wanda siding with psyche that sack of shit
son
Fucking Alex decided that she's gonna really go to bot for Trisha
Trisha
she made AI videos of Trish, she made AI videos of fucking Alec making her look the worst of the worst, a pig, a black pig of all things, race this fucking shit, I've never done that to you, fucking Alec, I never will, never, never.
This is why I know pussies exist and people are willing to bend over to racist
Fucking shit behavior. Krakadana. You're freaking like a bending over to Krakadana. Yikes, a whole risk I can lost
I take a fucking, I'm going to go down to the grave and tell you I lost respect for you.
Shrimpcake, are you watching?
I fucking lost all respect for fucking Alex.
When she fucking mudded, stupid, fucking, stupid J-Dog of all people in her chat.
Wow.
Talk about fucking campaigns and propaganda.
Talk about nasty behavior, I
Never did shit to you
never
Never you did it to me and Jim Nick
You know what I tell you
What it was the last word I said lay off a fucking Trisha. No talk about her fucking kid and you listen to me
Now you're gonna gank up on me
Tenfold the best your fucking ass and your fucking fake ass
Big fucking up. You want your attention? You got it
You got balls
You are fucking like a whole shit about it tomorrow. I
Stand out what I stand on. I don't like Zaya. I never have never well
Never you will never fucking find me liking Zaya
But guess what?
Guess what?
Alexandra
You are willing to meet up with him. Not me
You promoted fucking pub for a month
Stream of the fucking fucking year or what stream you're over the fucking month or watch
For people that talk dirty on you
And I hope that you bend over backwards and get what you fucking really deserve and what is that?
information that somebody might actually
You know, you know make some kind of like
Peace with you when I never had beef with you
Mm-hmm. Fuck you
Fuck you
You heard I'm not scared of you
Alex, good luck to you. Go live tomorrow and like, uh, pump her and put some diapers on fucking, uh,
site T, and his stupid ass tantrum, because guess what? I got 60 fucking messages from him,
fucking like saying he's gonna come at suicide and he's gonna fucking put everything in my hand.
I got many messages from fucking stupid ass that fucking jerk bag.
Black Hat Andy a year ago. He called me and his fucking the police department called me begging for help
What did you do turn a fucking blind eye went to your convenience? What the fuck did happen to me?
I took this shit for it
And this is who i'm still here
This is why I'm still here because I have a lot to fucking stay and a lot to fucking expose
I'm not gonna do it in one fucking dish. I'm gonna give it to you a little type of increment
I'm not a fucking fool like you guys
Stupid fucking dumbasses. Oh my god. Did you hear the breaking you?
Tisha was simped on by like a fucking blockhead auntie.
You know what blockhead auntie did to me?
He lived in my county.
He left 25 miles away from me.
He asked me to fucking make Lego pieces with him. He keeps sending me fucking kitty pictures. I
Love this cat. Look at my cat. Be that you look great for your age be that
You know how he turned on me because I said don't fuck with fucking Jim Nick
And he said you're a fucking lead brain and he turned on me and you know what?
Jim Nick with all the respect
You also bent you.
I'll never bend for any of you guys.
None of you guys.
I showed a little bit of fucking samples and nobody fucking believed me.
What fucking stupid blackout did to me for a fucking almost a year.
Making thumbnails out of me.
Callin' me a camel jockey.
Like all that.
Turn a blind eye.
Come as a bitch
You want to see it ask for it. Do you really want the truth? I'll give it to you
If you want it, or do you want to be in your stupid fucking perception? Oh
Illusional fucking whatever
With psyche psyche. Oh my god psyche psyche is such a is so perfect. He's so intertwined with positivity and the world
fucking ridiculous?
That goes pathetic.
I've been encouraging him for fucking months and months
and months and months and months,
telling him to get his shit together
and get his axe together.
And we got a person over here.
Oh, I'm gonna get your shit together.
Did it work?
Mm-mm, it turned out.
And it felt really bad.
Really bad.
I'm not scared of anybody, no sama, not nobody. Nobody. You want my address?
Get already put it out there. Get your turtle.
How about you look at some of the fucking feedback by fucking stupid ass blackout Andy for years?
For years. Call me a fucking channel.
Do you ever defend me?
No, you're going to defend somebody and talk shit about you.
I called you a black pig, like fucking Trisha.
Imagine, imagine, yikes, yikes, bend over a little bit more, you fucking bitches.
I trusted you as a fucking like a person, a friend, and I told you I'm afraid of you.
I'll create on my fucking stupid panel, and on top of it all, you're gonna go go live
and be like, I'm gonna go smash it!
But now we got this fucking stupid psyche making fun of me saying that I made fun of his nose.
I said he had a fucking nose job when I never did.
We got this fucking like a J-dog that's over there fucking talk his shit and we got him modded for you.
hey psyche remember every motherfucking dyke when you send me pictures of your
fucking family I will never expose that bitch but you know don't make that last
minute words be suicide you want me to show your 65 fucking messages call I
I better. I better.
Sorry Alexander, you told me not to do it while you were doing the whole, you know, you know, like, up, upgrading mother to mother fucker.
Have you ever felt like he fucking did it? Like, I will fuck him up!
Apologize to me fucking whore. You bitch. You fucking bitch. Bye. Bye. Make my old like whole fucking shorts about your fucking stupid behavior
Alexander mayors you're stupid. I'm gonna say it market right now. You have
Fucking J-Dog as a mod. You're stupid. S-2-U-P-I with a capital letter G with a
dick and like everything. You're stupid. That guy fucking docks me, bitch.
He docks me. And you think he's a little coolio?
You can't hold a candle to her a beta. You don't you're not even a porn star. Are you kidding me? You can't handle it
You can't touch that
Everybody's
I'm just gonna say it's just too bad for like
Your best friends with her now she's stupid
People that you see me being that's how it works
Oh my god, she's using the baby voice because she's scared of Alex. That's why we floppy floppy floppy floppy floppy
Yeah
I'm gonna play like I don't know what's going on and this person is such a magnificent human being
And I know I know them so well because we connects like so fully
But we are like the same people
People may be jealous. I'm blah blah blah
love
I know the truth and I'm gonna fucking show it whether it comes to Trisha
Lisha who's gonna talk shit about my fucking she said I pull my cats whiskers
out and I fuck my uncle but thank you so much Alexander Muir for not ever
acknowledging that thank you so much for like
Uh, you know, just messing the blind eye to the way the people that you see me.
Well, what, Chris, Crystal Murray told me last night, Dad, you're dead.
You're dead.
I never did that to you.
I never made AI or anything like that.
You're dead.
I had to ask her to fuck her two nights ago.
You lost to you, you fucking dumb bitches.
Birds of the same fucking feather will flock together, and I'm gonna fucking be solo.
I am a fucking gonna be a solo bitch.
Easy.
You pull your cat whiskers out
It's not
I'll get you put you want to admit that's funny. Okay. Well
Go fuck yourself you fucking piece of shit
Okay
Yeah
okay somebody like pulling a cat with their eyes is like that's disgusting like they're
peripherally that's that's that's animal torture uh cats don't have a word to say he can't say
i don't like that or i do but i did research that's jeffrey domership i really like people
like that on my panel and i'm gonna eliminate like things like that it's funny to them i am
that I am like a cat's liquor out I wouldn't even pull your mustache out good
time that's like really brutal what you see I treat my cat I love my cat
Talking about my fucking cat, fucking disgusting motherfucker.
I treat my cat with the most love.
It's funny, she knows.
We'll go, giggle and laugh, where you think it's fucking funny.
Fuck him. Fuck these people. Fuck him.
Disgusting. It's funny. It's so funny. Do your research.
Pulling a cat fucking whiskers is like taking out their fucking rear-view fucking mirrors.
It's their perfect vision. It will take your balance out. It's not fucking funny. Okay? It's not funny ever.
I would never harm an animal.
I would never even like-
You're disgusting.
I fucking don't like you thing anymore.
You better fucking apologize.
It's not fucking funny.
What?
Who said that?
Who did I do?
I don't know if she's gonna have a,
somebody said some hot cat whiskers
to her or something.
I don't know.
Don't fucking tuck her arm.
Fucking cat.
done wrong to you. Please shit all you want about me. If anything happens to those fucking cats,
I would fucking like not even want to be here. So what do they do to you? All you motherfuckers,
all you fucking assholes, who the fuck yourselves? Oh my fucking s- like
little fucking whiskers out you fucking pieces of shit you fucking I hate you so bad I hate you
I hate you say it again I hope you fuck hey let me in baby come on
I never said anything like that I love my cat I don't pull its whiskers you knew
Yeah, I mean, you know what? My boyfriend can't with his beehive, you're sick son of a bitch.
I don't have anything about being with you, you don't got, you don't have that.
John yeah, are you okay?
What's that?
Demi Rose is back. What's up girl? Oh
Hey, it's just me. It's just me to say that you and Janet are evil people
Oh, and by the way, we have a mole. His name is alibaster computer. He was in the voice chat
He's like his voice right now. He he he you he gave us like his address. He's like
Just so we can fool everybody he's been he's been just like the information. Did I hear that?
You need to defend yourself right now.
Hey, what's up, Trace?
I'm not defending myself because this is so stupid.
I wouldn't do that to you.
So why did you come to the voice chat this afternoon?
You can't keep interrupting people.
There's guys interrupting.
You're not going to come here and be through.
Yeah, you need to calm down.
Like seriously, we having a nice show.
Joe, Joe, if you can, if you can just give this
just for a moment, brother.
You know, you can just let
you know, don't talk to women
like that. You shouldn't
That's not nice. You shouldn't.
You shouldn't be. You shouldn't
be talking to like that. He
lost his dog like not too long
or I care. Okay, but I just
listen. Janet. Janet's going
And that's uh, that's something I'm interested in. Can you just kind of share your experience like what happened when you were doing that?
Yes, actually.
Yeah, there was a guy that I was in love with and I really couldn't like be with him and he was older than me and I remember like I went to a tech school when I was in high school.
So I was with.
to be here
well i'm going to play it for you
and i don't have that many clips
maybe go to the site
uh... it's called
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Oh
I'm sorry. I didn't see it wasn't on. I'm sorry. I didn't see it was on. Hey, I'm here. I thought I was on. I was playing videos. Sorry
Okay, anyway, I didn't want to be distracted. I was trying to like I was playing some videos
But I didn't have them on the screen. I was watching from over there trying to make this play play them one after the other
But I'm sorry, but that you apologize
Yeah, I don't know everyone's coming out today in the chat. It seems like it's like, you know interesting a lot of people
Let me see. What do I have?
maybe
Check out
Isn't it nice to finally be outside on such a beautiful day?
Yes, and I've packed us a delicious chicken picnic.
It's pesky bee.
Hmm, he seems upset about something.
I wonder what will happen.
It makes you sad, doesn't it?
But there's so much hatred in the world.
I hope you don't mind if I ask you a question.
A little baby pigeon.
Have you ever wondered why we're here?
What's it all about you? No idea.
And every way you look, all you see is hatred.
And darkness, death and fear
But you know it doesn't have to be
I hate you, and you hate me
Cause even though we're different
It doesn't make a difference
And we can live in harmony
No, you don't know who I am
But maybe I can hold your hand
And together we can understand about love
Huh?
I feel tingly.
Yes, that's love my friend.
And it's time for you to learn all about it.
feel like life's unfair because everybody hates you and no one cares but if you follow me maybe you
will see the love is everywhere. What is love? Is it in disguise? No it's a feeling deep inside
because I'm hungry. No you're lonely. I can see it in your eyes. I don't understand. Don't worry
you will soon. Come and meet some of my friends they know all about love. Come on just do it with
Maybe we should follow him, or we'll get left behind.
Yes, but there's lots of chicken left. I'd like to eat the chicken.
I'd also like to eat the chicken. Let's do that instead.
So here we are with all my friends, and they love you, all of them.
Yes, we do.
It is true. We love you.
You love us too.
I love you too, Furry Boy.
Harder.
Now we've eaten the chicken, I don't know what to do.
Maybe we should look for our friend. Isn't that what friends do?
And we have finished the chicken picnic.
To love each other is to care, to be kind
And to share!
I love my friends, I want to give them a hug
I made this for you because I love you so much
I love my pet co-tea, the crab
I love this tree and I love this stick and I love this mud
No, no, no, that's all how it's done
You must save your love for your special one
My special one?
Everyone has a special one
Even me?
Yes, it's true, but do not worry, you're confused, but that's okay. Let me put it another way.
This is the story of Michael, the loneliest boy in town.
This is the story of Michael, the ugliest boy in town.
A year week they called him a freak, so he lived on his own underground.
He lived on his own underground. He lived on his own underground.
You see, everyone has a special one!
Even Michael!
Your heartbeat's hard like a big love drum
Calling for your special one
So be patient, because just moving
Your special one will come
He's made for her
And she's made for him
That's the way it's always been
And it's perfect
And it's pure
And it's protected with a ring
That's the way that...
Like a flower, it grows and grows, and it's forever, and forever, and now we all worship
our king, our king, his name is Malcolm, he is the king of love, we must feed him, we
must feed him gravel, or he becomes angry.
And this is your chance to start anew, and all we're asking you to do, is change your name, and clean your brain, forget about anything you ever knew, and your heart will burn its home, and our love will never come.
Now wear this ring, and join the chain, and you will never be alone.
Oh, there you are. We've been looking for you all afternoon.
We're sorry we upset you, but look, we've bought you the last boiled egg to cheer you up.
I guess it must be because we love you.
For me?
Father!
Eh! Pesky bee!